Aladdin Company Records Collection 1907-1989 (bulk 1940-1982)
Clarke Historical Library
- Aladdin Company Collection - Series #3, (Advertising, 1907-1985)
  - Records, Art Work and Floor Plans (primarily for annual catalog) - “Folder 4”, Nantucket: Floor plan 2 (1950), Narragansett: Floor plan 1 (nd) and floor plan 2 (nd), Nassau: Floor plan 1 (nd) and floor plan 2 (nd), Newport: Floor plan 1 (1952), 5 (1949), 5 1952), and 6 (1954), Newton: Floor plan 1 (1970), and floor plan 2 (1970), Norfolk: Floor plan 1 (1952) and 3 (1950-1952), Northport: Floor plan 1 (nd) and floor plan 2 (nd), Oakland: Floor plan 1 (1960) and 2 (1960), Palm Springs: Floor Plan 1 (1952), floor plan (1957) and 3 (1951-1952), Palo Alto: Floor plan 1 (1950-1952), 2 (1950, 1951-1952), Palomar: Floor plan 1 (1952), 2 (1952) floor plan 3 (1952), 4 (1957), and 5 small picture and prints, Parkway: Floor plan 1 (nd), 1 (1952-1953), 2 (1952), floor plan 3 (nd), floor plan 4 (nd), 4 (1952), 5 (1950-1952), and print for floor plans 1, 4, and 5, Parkwood: Floor plan 1964, Pasadena: Floor plan 1 (1950-1952), 1 (1955) and 2 (1950-1952), Pilgrim: Floor plan 2 (1950) (attic stair), 2 (1950), 2 (attic stair), 4 (1950-1952) and 5 (1950-1952), New Pilgrim: Floor plan (1949) (attic stair), Pinecrest: Floor plan 1 (1956), and 2 (1956), Pinewood: Floor plan 1 (1950), and floor plan 2 (1950), Plaza: Floor plan (nd), 1 (1953), 2 (1953), floor plan 2 (nd), floor plan 2 (nd), 4 (1955), 1 (1973) and 3 (1973), Pomoma: Floor plan 2 (1952) (also as Old Potomac 2), and 3 (1952), Portage: Floor plan (1969), Port Austin: Floor plan 1 (nd), floor plan 2 (nd), Port Hope: Floor plan 1 (nd) and floor plan 2 (nd), Potomac: Floor plan (1949) and 2 (nd), Preston: Floor plan (1958) and floor plan (1958) print, Princeton: Floor plan (1966) and 2 (1966), Rambler: Floor plan 1 (1954), 2 (1954) and 3 (1954), Redwood: Floor plan 1 (1950-1952), 2 (1950-1952) and 3 (1950-1952) and 4 (1957), Rio Grande: Floor plan 1 (1952), 2 (1952), 3 (1952) and 4 (1955), Richmond: Floor plan (1965), Ridgewood: Floor plan (1967), Riviera: Floor plan (1960), 1 (1978) and 2 (1978), Roanoke: Floor plan (1957), Rockport: Floor plan 2 (1952), 4 (1952), 5 (1952), 6(1949) (with attic stair), Rose Wood: Floor plan 1 (1950-1952), 2 (1950-1952), and 3 (1950-1952), Royton: Floor plan 1 (1953), 2 (1953) and 3 (1953), Salem: Floor plan 1 (nd), floor plan 2 (nd), San Diego: Floor plan 1 (nd) floor plan 2 (nd), floor plan 3 (nd), 4 (1955), and 5 (1957), Santa Barbara: Floor plan 1 (1952-1953), 2 (1952-1953) and 3 (1953), Santa Fe: Floor plan 1 (1955) and alternate plan; 2 (1952) and 3 (1954),1949-1978, undated (Box 64, Folder 1218)
  - Records, Art Work and Floor Plans (primarily for annual catalog) - “Folder 5”, Santa Rose: Floor plan 1 (1953) and 2 (1953), Saratoga: Floor plan 1 (1956), Savannah: Floor plan (1966) and 2 (1974), Selma: Floor plan (1969), Shadyland: Floor plan 1 (1956) and 2 (1956), Sharlear: Floor plan 1 (1961), floor plan 2 (nd) and 2 (1961), Shelburne: Floor plan 2 (1952) and 2 (1952), Shelby: Floor plan (1957), Sherwood: Floor plan 1 (1965) and 2 (1965), Sierra: Floor plan 1 (1972), 2 (1972), 3 (1972) and 4 (1972), Sparta: Floor plan (1971) (Includes second and third floor level); floorplan 2 (nd) (Includes second and third floor level), St. Lawrence: Floor plan 1 (1950) and 2 (1950), Stratford: Floor plan 2 (1980), Summerset: Floor plan (1950-1952), Sunbeam: Floor plan (1949), Sunset: Floor plan 1 (1950), 2 (1950) and floor plan for second floor (nd), Sunshine B: Floor plan (1952), Sunshine D: Floor plan (1951-1952), Sunshine E: Floor plan (1950-1952), Sylvan: Floor plan 1 (1952), 2 (1952) and 3 (1954), Tacoma: Floor plan (1957), Topeka: Floor plan 1 (1957), 2 (1958); printed floor plans for floor plan 1 (1957) and floor plan 2 (1958), Trenton: Floor plan (1962) and 2 (1965), Tulane: Floor plan (1957) and utility room and garage floor plan (1957), Tulsa: Floor plan 1 (1955) and 2 (1955), Vassa: Floor plan 2 (nd), and floor plan 3 (nd), Ventura: Floor plan 1 (nd), floor plan 2 (nd) and floor plan 3 (nd), Ventura 1-A: Floor plan 1 (nd), Vernon: Floor plan 1 (1960), 2 (1960) and 3 (1960), Vinewood: Floor plan 1 (1952) and 2 (1952), Wenona: Floor plan 1 (1950) and 2 (1950), Westport: Floor plan (nd), Williams Burge: Floor plan (1952), Wilshire: Floor plan 1 (1956), 2 (1956) and 3 (1966), Winston: Floor plan 1 (1952) and 5 (1952), Woodland: Floor plan 1 (1953) and 2 (1953), Yorkshire: Floor plan (1969), Yorktown: Floor plan 1 (1953) and 2 (1953), Miscellaneous Floor Plans: Floor plan (1962) (plywood sheeting)/ Floor plan (1949) (Cedar shake)/ Floor plan (1960s or 1970s)/ Floor plan (nd) (Right wall),1949-1980, undated (Box 64, Folder 1219)
- Aladdin Company Collection - Series #4 (Order Department)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Maryland 1,1979 (Box 65, Folder 1220)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Maine 1,1979 (Box 65, Folder 1221)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Kentucky 1,1979 (Box 65, Folder 1222)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Kentucky 2,1979 (Box 65, Folder 1222b)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Indiana 4,1979 (Box 65, Folder 1223)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Massachusetts 1,1979 (Box 65, Folder 1224)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Illinois 5,1979 (Box 65, Folder 1225)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Illinois 4,1979 (Box 65, Folder 1226)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Illinois 3,1979 (Box 65, Folder 1227)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Illinois 2,1979 (Box 65, Folder 1228)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Indiana 3,1979 (Box 65, Folder 1229)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Indiana 2,1979 (Box 65, Folder 1230)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Indiana 1,1979 (Box 65, Folder 1231)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Illinois 7,1979 (Box 65, Folder 1232)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Illinois 6,1979 (Box 65, Folder 1233)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Missouri 2,1978 (Box 65, Folder 1234)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Missouri 3,1978 (Box 65, Folder 1235)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Missouri 4,1978 (Box 65, Folder 1236)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Connecticut 1,1979 (Box 65, Folder 1237)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Delaware 1,1979 (Box 65, Folder 1238)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Illinois 1,1979 (Box 65, Folder 1239)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 New York 3,1978 (Box 66, Folder 1240)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 New York 2,1978 (Box 66, Folder 1241)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 New York 1,1978 (Box 66, Folder 1242)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Michigan 10,1978 (Box 66, Folder 1243)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Michigan 9,1978 (Box 66, Folder 1244)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Michigan 8,1978 (Box 66, Folder 1245)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Michigan 7,1978 (Box 66, Folder 1246)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Michigan 6,1978 (Box 66, Folder 1247)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 New Hampshire 1,1978 (Box 66, Folder 1248)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 New Jersey 1,1978 (Box 66, Folder 1249)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 New Jersey 2,1978 (Box 66, Folder 1250)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 New Jersey 3,1978 (Box 66, Folder 1251)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Michigan 2,1978 (Box 66, Folder 1252)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Michigan 3, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 1253)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Michigan 4,1978 (Box 66, Folder 1254)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Michigan 5,1978 (Box 66, Folder 1255)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Illinois 3,1981 (Box 67, Folder 1256)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Illinois 1,1981 (Box 67, Folder 1257)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Connecticut 1,1981 (Box 67, Folder 1258)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Missouri 1,1980 (Box 67, Folder 1259)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Iowa 1,1980 (Box 67, Folder 1260)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Delaware 1,1981 (Box 67, Folder 1261)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Missouri 2,1980 (Box 67, Folder 1262)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Wisconsin 1,1980 (Box 67, Folder 1263)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Wisconsin 2,1980 (Box 67, Folder 1264)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Wisconsin 1,1980 (Box 67, Folder 1265)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 West Virginia 1,1980 (Box 67, Folder 1266)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Virginia 1,1980 (Box 67, Folder 1267)
  - Records, Mailing lists - Rhode Island,undated (Box 67, Folder 1268)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Indiana 3,1981 (Box 67, Folder 1269)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Indiana 2,1981 (Box 67, Folder 1270)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Illinois 7,1981 (Box 67, Folder 1271)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Illinois 5,1981 (Box 67, Folder 1272)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Indiana 1,1981 (Box 67, Folder 1273)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Illinois 6,1981 (Box 67, Folder 1274)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Illinois 4,1981 (Box 67, Folder 1275)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Illinois 2,1981 (Box 67, Folder 1276)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Illinois 6,1980 (Box 68, Folder 1277)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Illinois 4,1980 (Box 68, Folder 1278)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Illinois 2,1980 (Box 68, Folder 1279)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Kentucky 1,1980 (Box 68, Folder 1280)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Illinois 7,1980 (Box 68, Folder 1281)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Illinois 3,1980 (Box 68, Folder 1282)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Illinois 1,1980 (Box 68, Folder 1283)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Connecticut 1,1980 (Box 68, Folder 1284)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Maine 1,1980 (Box 68, Folder 1285)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Kentucky 1,1980 (Box 68, Folder 1286)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Delaware 1,1980 (Box 68, Folder 1287)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Indiana 4,1980 (Box 68, Folder 1288)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Indiana 3,1980 (Box 68, Folder 1289)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Indiana 1,1980 (Box 68, Folder 1290)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Indiana 2,1980 (Box 68, Folder 1291)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Illinois 5,1980 (Box 68, Folder 1292)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 New York 3,1979 (Box 69, Folder 1293)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 New York 2,1979 (Box 69, Folder 1294)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 New York 1,1979 (Box 69, Folder 1295)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 New Jersey 2,1979 (Box 69, Folder 1296)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Michigan 7,1979 (Box 69, Folder 1297)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Michigan 6,1979 (Box 69, Folder 1298)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Michigan 5,1979 (Box 69, Folder 1299)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Michigan 4,1979 (Box 69, Folder 1300)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Michigan 8,1979 (Box 69, Folder 1301)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Michigan 9,1979 (Box 69, Folder 1302)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Michigan 10,1979 (Box 69, Folder 1303)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 New Hampshire,1979 (Box 69, Folder 1304)
  - Records, Mailing lists - New Jersey,undated (Box 69, Folder 1305)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Michigan 3,1979 (Box 69, Folder 1306)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Michigan 2,1979 (Box 69, Folder 1307)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Michigan 1,1979 (Box 69, Folder 1308)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Pennsylvania 1, 1978 (Box 70, Folder 1309)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Ohio 9,1978 (Box 70, Folder 1310)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Ohio 8,1978 (Box 70, Folder 1311)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Ohio 2,1978 (Box 70, Folder 1312)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Ohio 3,1978 (Box 70, Folder 1313)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Ohio 1,1978 (Box 70, Folder 1314)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Ohio 4,1978 (Box 70, Folder 1315)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Ohio 5,1978 (Box 70, Folder 1316)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Ohio 6,1978 (Box 70, Folder 1317)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Ohio 7,1978 (Box 70, Folder 1318)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 New York 4,1978 (Box 70, Folder 1319)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 New York 5,1978 (Box 70, Folder 1320)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 New York 6,1978 (Box 70, Folder 1321)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 New York 7,1978 (Box 70, Folder 1322)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 New York 1,1981 (Box 71, Folder 1323)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 New Jersey 2,1981 (Box 71, Folder 1324)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Michigan 10,1981 (Box 71, Folder 1325)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 New Jersey 1,1981 (Box 71, Folder 1326)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 New Hampshire 1,1981 (Box 71, Folder 1327)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - Stickers,undated (Box 72, Folder 1328)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - “How to Read Claims”,undated (Box 72, Folder 1329)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - W2 forms – 1964,1964 (Box 72, Folder 1330)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - W2 forms – 1985,1985 (Box 72, Folder 1331)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - W2 forms – 1984,1984 (Box 72, Folder 1332)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - W2 forms – 1982,1982 (Box 72, Folder 1333)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - W2 forms – 1981,1981 (Box 72, Folder 1334)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - W2 forms – 1980,1980 (Box 72, Folder 1335)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - W2 forms – 1979,1979 (Box 72, Folder 1336)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - W2 forms – 1978,1978 (Box 72, Folder 1337)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - W2 forms – 1977,1977 (Box 72, Folder 1338)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - W2 forms – 1976/ Form 1099 – Int. 1976,1976 (Box 72, Folder 1339)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - W2 forms – 1975/ Form 1099 – Int. 1975,1975 (Box 72, Folder 1340)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - W2 forms – 1974/ Form 1099 – Int. 1974,1974 (Box 72, Folder 1341)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - W2 forms – 1973,1973 (Box 72, Folder 1342)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - W2 forms – 1972,1972 (Box 72, Folder 1343)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - W2 forms – 1971,1971 (Box 72, Folder 1344)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - W2 forms – 1970,1970 (Box 72, Folder 1345)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - W2 forms – 1969,1969 (Box 72, Folder 1346)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - W2 forms – 1968,1968 (Box 72, Folder 1347)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - W2 forms – 1967,1967 (Box 72, Folder 1348)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - W2 forms – 1966,1966 (Box 72, Folder 1349)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - W2 forms – 1965,1965 (Box 72, Folder 1350)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - Retail Invoices #04749 – 04806, 1973,1973 (Box 72, Folder 1351)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - Retail Invoices #04807 – 04859, 1974,1974 (Box 72, Folder 1352)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - Retail Invoices #04860 – 04951, 1975,1975 (Box 72, Folder 1353)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - Retail Invoices #4952 – 5000/ #2700 – 2716, 1976,1976 (Box 72, Folder 1354)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - Retail Invoices #02717 – 02803, 1977,1977 (Box 72, Folder 1355)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - Retail Invoices #02804 – 02830, 1978,1978 (Box 72, Folder 1356)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - Retail Invoices #02831 – 02887, 1979,1979 (Box 72, Folder 1357)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - Retail Invoices #02888 – 02902, 1980,1980 (Box 72, Folder 1358)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - Retail Invoices #02903 – 02912, 1981,1981 (Box 72, Folder 1359)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - Wholesale & Retail Invoices #2913 – 2995, 1982,1982 (Box 72, Folder 1360)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - Retail Invoices #2996 – 3005, 1983,1983 (Box 72, Folder 1361)
  - Records, Financial Information: tax information: W2, 1099, instructions, insurance claims - #3006 – 3033, 1984,1984 (Box 72, Folder 1362)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Pennsylvania 3,1980 (Box 73, Folder 1363)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Pennsylvania 5,1980 (Box 73, Folder 1364)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Pennsylvania 7,1980 (Box 73, Folder 1365)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Ohio 9,1980 (Box 73, Folder 1366)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Pennsylvania 2,1980 (Box 73, Folder 1367)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Vermont 1,1980 (Box 73, Folder 1368)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 West Virginia 2,1980 (Box 73, Folder 1369)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Pennsylvania 4,1980 (Box 73, Folder 1370)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Pennsylvania 6,1980 (Box 73, Folder 1371)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Pennsylvania 8,1980 (Box 73, Folder 1372)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Virginia 2,1980 (Box 73, Folder 1373)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Pennsylvania 1,1980 (Box 73, Folder 1374)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Ohio 2,1980 (Box 73, Folder 1375)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Ohio 4,1980 (Box 73, Folder 1376)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Ohio 6,1980 (Box 73, Folder 1377)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1980 Ohio 6,1980 (Box 73, Folder 1378)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 West Virginia 3,1978 (Box 74, Folder 1379)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 West Virginia 2,1978 (Box 74, Folder 1380)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 West Virginia 1,1978 (Box 74, Folder 1381)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Virginia 2,1978 (Box 74, Folder 1382)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Wisconsin 1,1978 (Box 74, Folder 1383)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Wisconsin 2,1978 (Box 74, Folder 1384)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Wisconsin 4,1978 (Box 74, Folder 1385)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Iowa 1,1978 (Box 74, Folder 1386)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Minnesota 1,1978 (Box 74, Folder 1387)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Missouri 1,1978 (Box 74, Folder 1388)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Virginia 1,1978 (Box 74, Folder 1389)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Pennsylvania 5,1978 (Box 74, Folder 1390)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Pennsylvania 4,1978 (Box 74, Folder 1391)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Vermont 1,1978 (Box 74, Folder 1392)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Rhode Island 1,1978 (Box 74, Folder 1393)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Pennsylvania 2,1978 (Box 74, Folder 1394)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Pennsylvania 3,1978 (Box 74, Folder 1395)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Pennsylvania 6,1978 (Box 74, Folder 1396)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1978 Pennsylvania 7,1978 (Box 74, Folder 1397)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Ohio 2,1981 (Box 75, Folder 1398)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Missouri 2,1981 (Box 75, Folder 1399)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Missouri 1,1981 (Box 75, Folder 1400)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Minnesota 1,1981 (Box 75, Folder 1401)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Iowa 1,1981 (Box 75, Folder 1402)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Wisconsin 2,1981 (Box 75, Folder 1403)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Wisconsin 1,1981 (Box 75, Folder 1404)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Ohio 7,1981 (Box 75, Folder 1405)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Ohio 8,1981 (Box 75, Folder 1406)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Pennsylvania 1,1981 (Box 75, Folder 1407)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Pennsylvania 2,1981 (Box 75, Folder 1408)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Ohio 6,1981 (Box 75, Folder 1409)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Ohio 5,1981 (Box 75, Folder 1410)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Ohio 4,1981 (Box 75, Folder 1411)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Ohio 3,1981 (Box 75, Folder 1412)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Pennsylvania 3,1981 (Box 75, Folder 1413)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Pennsylvania 4,1981 (Box 75, Folder 1414)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Pennsylvania 5,1981 (Box 75, Folder 1415)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Pennsylvania 6,1981 (Box 75, Folder 1416)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Missouri 2,1979 (Box 76, Folder 1417)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 West Virginia 1,1979 (Box 76, Folder 1418)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Virginia 2,1979 (Box 76, Folder 1419)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Virginia 1,1979 (Box 76, Folder 1420)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Vermont 1,1979 (Box 76, Folder 1421)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Rhode Island 1,1979 (Box 76, Folder 1422)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Pennsylvania 7,1979 (Box 76, Folder 1423)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 West Virginia 2,1979 (Box 76, Folder 1424)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Wisconsin 11979 (Box 76, Folder 1425)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Wisconsin 2,1979 (Box 76, Folder 1426)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Iowa 1,1979 (Box 76, Folder 1427)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Minnesota 1,1979 (Box 76, Folder 1428)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Missouri 1,1979 (Box 76, Folder 1429)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Pennsylvania 6,1979 (Box 76, Folder 1430)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Pennsylvania 5,1979 (Box 76, Folder 1431)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Pennsylvania 4,1979 (Box 76, Folder 1432)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1979 Pennsylvania 3,1979 (Box 76, Folder 1433)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 New York 5,1981 (Box 77, Folder 1434)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 New York 6,1981 (Box 77, Folder 1435)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 New York 7,1981 (Box 77, Folder 1436)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Pennsylvania 1,1981 (Box 77, Folder 1437)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Rhode Island 1,1981 (Box 77, Folder 1438)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Vermont 1,1981 (Box 77, Folder 1439)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Virginia 1,1981 (Box 77, Folder 1440)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 Virginia 2,1981 (Box 77, Folder 1441)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 West Virginia 1,1981 (Box 77, Folder 1442)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 West Virginia 2,1981 (Box 77, Folder 1443)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 New York 4,1981 (Box 77, Folder 1444)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 New York 3,1981 (Box 77, Folder 1445)
  - Records, Mailing lists - 1981 New York 2,1981 (Box 77, Folder 1446)